Time Inc. Time Covers 1923-2015 MS 3009-RG 32
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Time Covers
1923-2015
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 32
12 Linear feet in 12 record cartons
The Time Inc. Time Covers contains a chronological run of detached covers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Arrangement Note
Organized chronologically.
Scope and Contents Note
Time Covers contains a collection of covers removed from the rest of the magazine dating from 1923 through July 2015. Later dates sometimes include the entire magazine. This is a collection created by the Time Inc. Library and Archives.
Corporate libraries -- New York (State) -- New York.; Corporation records.; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Corporations -- History.; Library resources; Organization files.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Time, inc. -- Archives.; Time, inc. -- History.
- Time Covers, 1923-1929 (Offsite-box 667)
- Time Covers, 1929-1942 (Offsite-box 668)
- Time Covers, 1943-1958 (Offsite-box 669)
- Time Covers, 1959-1974 (Offsite-box 670)
- Time Covers, 1975-1986 (Offsite-box 671)
- Time Covers, 1987-2000 (Offsite-box 672)
- Time Covers, 2001-2007 (Offsite-box 673)
- Time Covers, 2007-2009; (8 boxes) (Offsite-box 674)
- Time Covers, 2009-2011 (Offsite-box 2001)
- Time Covers, 2011-2013 (Offsite-box 2002)
- Time Covers, 2013-2014 (Offsite-box 2003)
- Time Covers, 2014-2015 (Offsite-box 2004)